

Website

www.devandreyit.ru



Telegram

@DevAndreyIT



devandreyit@gmail.com



Location

Russia, Ivanovo

EDUCATION

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

React / Redux / Redux Toolkit / TS / Router-dom / Axios / Formik **IT-INCUBATOR** 2021 - 2022

JAVASCRIPT MARATHON

Javascript and Promise basics

Zar Zakharov 2021

JAVASCRIPT MARATHON

Javascript basics Vladilen Minin

2021

КУРС ПО JS + REACT

JavaScript / React / Fetch API / Redux Udemy, Ivan Petrychenko 2020 - 2021

ENGINEER FOR TECHNICAL PROCESS AUTOMATION

Ivanovo State Power University 2008 - 2012

Andrey Shavelev

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

I am front-end developer with experience in creating SPA, using React, Redux, TypeScript. I am constantly developing my knowledge in depth and breadth, at the moment I develop the front-end part of the project, as well as actively studying the writing of the back-end. I am accustomed to quality and responsible approach to my work, always bring it to an end.

WORK EXPERIENCE

My work as a Front-end developer:

07.2022 - 09.2022 Project: Learning Cards

Stack: TS, React, Redux, Redux-Thunk, React Router DOM, Axios, Formik

02.2022 - 09.2022 Project: Social Network

Stack: TS, React, Redux, Redux-Thunk, React Router DOM, Axios, Formik

03.2022 - 08.2022 Project: Todolist

Stack: TS, React, Redux, Redux-Thunk, React Router DOM,

Axios, Formik, MUI, Storybook

04.2021 - 07.2022 Project: Restaurant app

Stack: JavaScript, Fetch API

03.2020 - 06.2020 Project: Elektronika24

WordPress website creation, administration, promotion

01.2019 - 04.2019 The website of the company "Service Computer"

WordPress website creation, administration, promotion

Service Engineer

2012 - 2021 Company: Service Computer

Specialist in the installation, setup, troubleshooting and repair of high-tech equipment

lavaScript

SKILLS





Material UI











GitHub



React





Storvbook



Unit tests







Rest API



